playcodemonkey.com 2019-02-07

# Privacy Policy | Coding Games for Kids | CodeMonkey

Last modified: January 21, 2019 

Because your privacy is important to us, we operate by the principles described herein. We have created this Privacy Policy in order to describe to you our practicing regarding the information that we collect and how we use it. By using our Website, service (the "Service") and/or accepting the Terms of Service (which you can review here), you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this Policy. Capitalized terms used and not otherwise defined herein, shall have the respective meanings ascribed to them under Terms of Service. 

###  1\. The information we collect and how we collect it

We explicitly ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (the “Personal Information“). For example, during the registration process we will ask you for your name and the business name, e-mail address and other information related to the Service. Personal Information is also collected when you contact our customer support, or send us other communication, and sign up for newsletters or special offers. Additional information collected by our Website (and the Service) may include your IP address, web pages that you visit and any other data normally stored in website logs (collectively, the “Information”). 

We may collect billing and account information for credit cards, payment cards or other payment systems from clients of paid versions of our Service and share this information with our billing and payment processors. We do not store credit card or payment card numbers after they have been forwarded to our billing and payment processors. 

You must be above 13 years old to join our Service. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from visitors under the age of 13. We only collect Personal Information through our Service from visitors under 13 where we have received the confirmation (via our Service and in accordance with our Terms of Service) of such student’s school and/or teacher to obtain the required consent for that student to use our Service and disclose the Personal Information, or where the parent of a child has signed the child up to use the Service. 

Like many other websites, we use "cookies" (a small file sent to your computer by a website to allow the website to store information which uniquely identifies you) or other similar software to collect data in order to assist our users and provide them with a more personal experience visits in our Website. You can always disable cookies at your browser, but please note that if you do so, some (or all) of the features and functionality of our Service may not be available to you. 

We may also use other technologies to collect anonymous non-personally identifiable information. Such information may include your IP address, browser type, referring website, site usage, and whether you opened emails you received from us. 

We may post our own clients testimonials on our Website which may contain personally identifiable information. We will obtain a customer's consent to post its name along with its testimonial (unless such information was made public by the customer itself). 

Our Website offers a blog to allow you to learn more about us. These areas of the site are intended for parents and teachers. You should be aware that any personally identifiable information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information you choose to submit in blogs or any other publicly accessible service or website. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us via email privacy@cm-studios.com. 

Our site includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from our own practices. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is subject to their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any website you visit. 

We store all the Information with Amazon Web Services ("AWS") and we encourage you to review AWS Terms of Service and Privacy Policy, as we will not be responsible for what AWS do with the Information. We do not disclose your Information to any third party or use it in any way, except in order to provide the Service, and as sets forth in our Terms of Use. 

You are not required to provide us with any information, although we may be unable to provide the Service without your information.

### 2\. What we do with your information

We may use your information in the following ways:   
(i) To provide the Service as well as for auditing and improving our Service.   
(ii) We may occasionally inform you of new features, functionality, services and products, and other promotions from CodeMonkey as well as send you periodic updates, tips and newsletters. You may always opt-out of receiving these correspondences from us by following the unsubscribe instructions included in each Newsletter. Note that regardless of your election, we may continue sending you notices to update you on revisions made to this Privacy Policy or to our Terms of Service.   
(iii) We may use and share Information with certain third-parties that help us operate our Website and Service (e.g. cloud provider, email distribution service providers and other similar service providers). When we use such third parties, we restrict them from using or disclosing the information, except as required to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements. Personal information of our users will not be shared with third parties for marketing purposes.   
(iv) We may share Information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our services.   
(v) We reserve the right to disclose your Information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, or court order. 

We will retain your Information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide our Service. You may cancel your account at any time via the interface of the Service. If you encounter any problem in cancelling your account and you wish that we no longer use or hold your Information, please contact us via privacy@cm-studios.com. We may also retain and use your Information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our Terms of Service. 

When you send an email or other communication to CodeMonkey, we may retain those communications in order to process and respond to your requests and improve our Service. Please do not send us any communication which contains confidential information. Since we are not able to evaluate whether such communication contains confidential information or not, we may retain or use any information relayed in such communication, and such retention or use shall not be deemed as a breach of our obligations. 

We may disclose general aggregate non-personal information about our users to potential business partners, investors, or the public, but we will not, without your specific permission, disclose any of your Personal Information to third parties. 

Except as described herein, we do not disclose your Information or share it with third parties. 

### 3\. Legal Basis for Processing Personal Information under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), CodeMonkey Studios Ltd.'s legal basis for collecting and using the Personal Information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Information we collect and the specific context in which we collect it. 

CodeMonkey Studios Ltd. may process your Personal Information because: 

  * We need to perform a contract with you;
  * You have given us permission to do so;
  * The processing is in our legitimate interests and is not overridden by your rights; or
  * To comply with any applicable law.

### 4\. Information Security

We use industry standard security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These measures include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

We restrict access to Personal Information to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our Service. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and we require all of them to agree to use your Personal Information solely for the purpose for which we provided it to them and in accordance with our privacy policy. 

###  5\. Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. CodeMonkey Studios Ltd. aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Information. 

If you wish to be informed what Personal Information we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us. 

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights: 

  * **The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.** Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Information directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you. 
  * **The right of rectification.** You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete. 
  * **The right to object.** You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Information. 
  * **The right of restriction.** You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information. 
  * **The right to data portability.** You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format. 
  * **The right to withdraw consent.** You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where CodeMonkey Studios Ltd. relied on your consent to process your personal information. 

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests. You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA). 

### 6\. Miscellaneous 

If CodeMonkey becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we may transfer all Information we have collected from our users in connection with such a transaction. However, the purchaser or successor entity will adhere by the terms under which your Information has been collected. If the purchaser or successor entity will not assume such responsibility, we will notify our users and enable them to request the permanent deletion of their information. 

If you believe that we have not adhered to our privacy policy, please notify us by email to privacy@cm-studios.com and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem. 

To make any requests for changes to your child’s account or requests for the removal of personal information collected about you or your child from our Service (as applicable), or to request that we stop the further collection or use of your or your child's personal information in connection with the Service (as applicable), please contact us at privacy@cm-studios.com. 

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, and you are a registered user of the Service, we will notify you by email. We will obtain prior parental consent if any changes we make to this Privacy Policy affect users under the age of 13 in a way that requires such consent under COPPA. 

This policy shall be construed in accordance with and governed for all purposes by the substantive laws of the State of Israel without regard to conflicts of law provisions. You agree that any claim or dispute you may have against the Company and its affiliates, directors, officers, employees and representatives must be resolved by a court located in Tel-Aviv, Israel, and waive any jurisdictional, venue or inconvenient forum objections to such courts. 

If you have any question about our privacy policy, please contact us using the following information: 

CodeMonkey Studios Ltd. 2345 Yale St. 1st Floor Palo Alto, CA 94306, USA 

1-888-299-3294 

|  {{ i18n.t('selected_language_will_be_default') }}   
---|---  
  
  * {{ i18n.t('locale.available_languages') }} 

  * | 

{{ prettyPrintLocale(locale.name) }} 

|   
---|---|---  
  
  * {{ i18n.t('locale.translated_by_our_community') }} 

  * | 

{{ prettyPrintLocale(locale.name) }} 

|   
---|---|---  

{{ i18n.t('cancel') }} 

| 

{{ i18n.t('set_language') }}   
  
---|---  
  
X

{{ i18n.t('signup.in_order_to_subscribe') }} 

### TEACHER

Classroom management, tracking and lesson plans. It's free to sign up!

### STUDENT

Join your classmates in the fun coding adventure

### Parent

Introduce your child to Computer Science and track their progress

{{ i18n.t('signup.free_trial_length', {days: trialLengthInDays()}) }} 

_{{ i18n.t('more_options') }}_

NEXT 

Complete your registration by filling you school's information 

NEXT 

### Your Trial Starts Today

You have 30 days to explore and enjoy CodeMonkey, add your students and more. 

### One Last Thing

An activation email was sent to your email address  ({{ emailAddress }})   
Click on the activation link in the email to continue. 

### Your Trial Starts Today

You have 14 days to explore and enjoy CodeMonkey, start coding, learning and building!. 

### One Last Thing

An activation email was sent to your email address  ({{ emailAddress }})   
Click on the activation link in the email to continue. 

 Go to dashboard 

The classroom code is a combination of numbers and letters, that will be given to you by your teacher. Using the classroom code will ensure you can view your classmates' progress and share challenges with them. 

YES, I HAVE A CLASSROOM CODE 

NO, I DON'T HAVE A CLASSROOM CODE 

Unfortunately this option is disabled for your age group.   
Please ask a parent or a guardian to sign up using their personal information.  Please let your teacher know, they will know what to do. 

Thank you for signing up.   
The backpack is ready and the bananas are waiting!   
So what do you want to do next? 

 START PLAYING   GO TO CLASS MANAGEMENT 

You will need this information to log back into your account: 

Username:  {{ userInfo.username }}

Password:  {{ userInfo.password }} {{ showAsPassword(userInfo.password) }}

Show

Click to download a copy

I saved my info, LET'S PLAY!

Thank you for signing up.   
The backpack is ready and the bananas are waiting!   
So what do you want to do next? 

Thank you for signing up.   
We sent you a confirmation email to ({{ emailAddress }}), please click on the link to confirm your email address. 

To activate your subscription, Click here

 GET CODIN'! 

_{{ i18n.t('more_options') }}_

ENTER YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS AND WE WILL SEND YOU A LINK TO CHANGE YOUR PASSWORD 

HELP ME! 

PLEASE CHECK YOUR MAILBOX TO RESET YOUR PASSWORD 

PLEASE CONTACT YOUR TEACHER TO RETRIEVE  
OR CHANGE YOUR PASSWORD 

No worries! Contact us and we will help you get back on CodeMonkey 

ENTER YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS AND WE WILL SEND YOU ANOTHER CONFIRMATION MESSAGE 

SEND 

Just a moment... 

You must confirm your email address  ({{ confirmation.email }})  before you can continue.   
Please check your inbox and click on the confirmation link. If it's not there, it might be in the spam folder. 

Send confirmation email again 

{{ inlineErrors }}
